ILR School Dean's Office Publications /3006
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Dean's Office Publications
1953-1958
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
/3006
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Publications (documents).
Stationery, blank forms, pamphlets, and article reprints from the Dean's Office.
3071657
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, November 18, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 07, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3085: ILR School Dean's Office Files /4014: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files /4028: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Records /4054: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files /4070: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Personnel Files /4082: ILR School Dean's Office Records /4100: ILR School Dean's Office "Report of the ILR Review Panel" Background Documentation /4144: ILR School Dean's Office Files Additional
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations --Administration.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Dean's Office
3071657
- Certificates, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Blank examples
- Invitations, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Calling Cards (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Stationery (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Personnel Forms (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Blank forms
- Abstracts and Annotations, 1955-1957 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Cornell International Industrial and Labor Relations Reports (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Cornell Conference Report Covers, 1955-1958 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Cornell Studies in Industrial and Labor Relations (Box 1, Folder 9)
- ILR: A School to Meet a Need (Box 1, Folder 10)
- ILR Bulletin, 1954-1958 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Industrial and Labor Relations Research in Universities, 1954; Text (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Bulletin 26 (1954:Dec.)
    Format: Text.
  - Item 2: The Evolution of Managerial Ideas in Industrial Relations, 1958; Text (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Bulletin 27 (Reissued March 1958). Edwin E. Witte.
  - Item 3: Corruption and Racketeering in the Labor Movement, 1958; Text (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Bulletin 38 (1958:Feb.). Philip Taft
  - Item 4: Democracy in the Labor Movement, 1958; Text (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Bulletin 39 (1958:Feb.). Joel Seidman.
- ILR Graduate Study, Text (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Flyers
- ILR Seminars and Conferences, 1953-1957 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Flyers and announcements
- ILResearch, 1954-1957 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: ILR Research, 1954; Text (Box 1, Folder 14)
    v.1:no.1 (1954:Dec.)
  - Item 2: ILR Research, 1957; Text (Box 1, Folder 14)
    v.3:no.3 (1957:Summer)
- Industrial and Labor Relations Review, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Publications of the ILR School, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- ILR Reprint Series, 1953-1958 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Human Relations in Industry, 1953; Text (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Reprint Series no.15. Ralph N. Campbell. Reprinted from NISA News, August 1953
  - Item 2: Postwar Wage Determination in the Netherlands, 1957; Text (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Reprint Series no.56. John P. Windmuller. Reprinted from The Annals of the American Academy of Political and Social Science, v.310 (1957:Mar.)
  - Item 3: Problems of Indian Trade Unionism, 1957; Text (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Reprint Series no.57. Oscar A. Ornati. Reprinted from The Annals of the American Academy of Political and Social Science, v.310 (1957:Mar.)
  - Item 4: Trade Unions in Malaya, 1957; Text (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Reprint Series no.58. J. Norman Parmer. Reprinted from The Annals of the American Academy of Political and Social Science, v.310 (1957:Mar.)
  - Item 5: Labor and Nationalism in the British Caribbean, 1957; Text (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Reprint Series no.59. George T. Daniel. Reprinted from The Annals of the American Academy of Political and Social Science, v.310 (1957:Mar.)
  - Item 6: The Italian Labor Movement in 1956: The Structure of Crisis, 1957; Text (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Reprint Series no.60. Maurice F. Neufeld. Reprinted from The Annals of the American Academy of Political and Social Science, v.310 (1957:Mar.)
  - Item 7: On the Ranking Problem, 1957; Text (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Reprint Series no.61. Isadore Blumen. Reprinted from Psychometrika, v.22:no.1 (1957:Mar.)
  - Item 8: Identifying the Problem Drinker on the Job, 1957; Text (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Reprint Series no.62. Harrison M. Trice. Reprinted from Personnel Magazine, May 1957.
  - Item 9: Alcoholism: Group Factors in Etiology and Therapy, 1956; Text (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Reprint Series no.63. Harrison M. Trice. Reprinted from Human Organization, v.15:no.2 (1956: Summer).
  - Item 10: The National War Labor Board: A View Against the Background of Grievance Disputes, 1957; Text (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Reprint Series no.64. Salvatore J. Bella. Reprinted from Labor Law Journal (1957:June)
  - Item 11: On Asking Indirect Questions, 1956; Text (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Reprint Series no.65. William F. White. Reprinted from Human Organization v.15:no.4 (1956:Winter)
  - Item 12: Dispute Settlement in the New York Longshore Industry, 1957; Text (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Reprint Series no.66. Vernon H. Jensen. Reprinted from Industrial and Labor Relations Review v.10:no.4 (1957:July)
  - Item 13: Regulation of Employee Benefit Programs, 1957; Text (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Reprint Series no.67. Duncan M. MacIntyre. Reprinted from Industrial and Labor Relations Review v.10:no.4 (1957:July)
  - Item 14: British and American Changes in Interindustry Wage Structure Under Full Employment, 1957; Text (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Reprint Series no.68. Pamela Haddy and N. Arnold Tolles. Reprinted from The Review of Economics and Statistics v.39:no.4 (1957:Nov.)
  - Item 15: Lockouts, 1958; Text (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Reprint Series no.69. Robert V. Sweetall and Stanley L. Aiges. Reprinted from Labor Law Journal, January 1958.
  - Item 16: The CIO Jurisdictional Dispute Experience, 1958; Text (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Reprint Series no.70. Seymour H. Lehrer. Reprinted from Industrial and Labor Relations Review, v.11:no.2 (1958:Jan.)
  - Item 17: Alcoholics Anonymous, 1958; Text (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Reprint Series no.71. Harrison M. Trice. Reprinted from The Annals of the American Academy of Political and Social Science, v.315 (1958:Jan.)
- Reprints, 1958; Text (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Alcoholics Anonymous, 1958; Text (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Harrison M. Trice. Reprinted from The Annals of the American Academy of Political and Social Science, v.315 (1958:Jan.)
  - Item 2: Lookouts, 1958; Text (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Robert V. Sweetall and Stanley L. Aiges. Reprinted from Labor Law Journal, January 1958